(Leonard:)Great.
(Sheldon(off):)I can't sleep.
(Leonard:)Well, I can, so shut up.
(Sheldon(off):)Do you realize that
in less than nine hours, Arthur Jeffries...
(Sheldon(off):)...a.k.a. Professor Proton,
will be in our apartment?
You know if you stay up all night,
you're going to be sleepy tomorrow.
(Leonard:)And a sleepy Sheldon is a cranky Sheldon.
And a cranky Sheldon...
(Leonard:)...is actually no different
than a regular Sheldon. Good night.
(Sheldon(off):)I'm thinking of wearing a tuxedo.
(Leonard:)That's not ridiculous. Good night.
(Sheldon(off):)Do you have cufflinks?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Just as well.
(Sheldon(off):)Where can you rent a tuxedo
at 3:00 in the morning?
(Leonard:)Okay. Good night.
(Sheldon(off):)Nice to meet you, Professor Proton.